The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world
that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A way from the moon's sky.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is what I am for?
And though I travel far
from where my search began,
over seas of green and shores of sand,
through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me,
some days somewhere I'll finally see
the light I will search for everywhere.
My money says that we lived through this.
A cloud road that goes straight up,
you might want to reconsider that bet.
I wonder if this is a natural
formation of the clouds.
There's nothing natural about this at all.
Look, the exit!
They put up a big sign
showing us! Godland?
What is Godland Skypiea?
This isn't the exit!
It's the entrance!
Ha ha ha!
There it is!
Sky Island!
Wait, didn't the sign
we passed say Skypiea?
Yeah, that's the same name scribbled
on the map that Lock found.
So, I guess that galleon that
fell on us actually did come here.
The last time they set eyes
on this was 200 years ago.
I'm amazed that this place has
stayed beautiful for so long.
You can smell the adventure.
Putin is the seaweed in summer.
Wait for me! I like adventure!
It's kind of shallow.
Usopp, did you hurt yourself? Hello?
Hey, is it just me or is this
whole place made of clouds?
Big fluffy ones.
I love this stuff.
Come on, let's go ashore. Yeah.
Wait, I'm coming with you guys.
Me too, but I got to change first.
Luffy, we may have a problem
with dropping anchor here.
There's no seabed at the
bottom of this cloud.
You know, I thought about
that, and who cares?
I love the way you think. Thanks.
Yeah, I want to play.
I'll butt down and check
this out, you guys.
The beach is actually fluffy.
It squishes between my
toes like marshmallow mud.
What the heck is marshmallow mud?
I don't know, but that's what it's like.
Well, regardless of how the ground
may feel, it sure is an amazing sight.
Better than I imagined it.
It's a piece of work for sure, but I
think our shipmates are overreacting.
Bugs me when they get all worked up.
When they get all worked up.
You're hurting me.
I said I was sorry.
We forgot about the South Bird.
We really should have let him go.
He'll never survive here.
I wouldn't sweat it.
Birds adapt very quickly
to their environments.
And if not, there seem to be
some people living up here.
Don't worry about it.
He'll be fine.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, the anchor!
All taken care of.
It hit the heavier cloud below, which
is what I think this place floats on.
That means that Sky Island
floats on a sea of cloud cover.
I wonder if it's stationary in the
sky or if it moves with the tide.
We could sit on deck all day
and pick this whole thing apart.
Come on, what fun would that be?
Fact is, most of this makes zero
sense, so let's make the best of it.
This is why we came here, you guys!
Welcome to Sky Island!
Come on!
If I can do this, so can you!
Just jump!
Swordsman, you joining us?
Yeah.
I'll be along soon.
The captain smells adventure. Huh.
I never stop to think of
any of this as adventurous.
Maybe I should reconsider my stance.
Uh, something about the squishiness of
this island makes me want to sleep all day.
Ahoy!
This is your captain speaking!
King,
I must inform you that
this place is too much
fun for me to make any
more captain decisions.
Aye, aye, captain.
What do you say we just
sit around and do nothing?
Huh?
Nothing sounds like a plan to me. Denied!
But denied means no!
Such mysterious-looking flowers.
I've never seen anything like them.
I wonder if they're balloonish
like that sea monster.
They'll pop when I pick one.
Uh, this is great.
Those marine losers can't follow
us up here so we can all cut loose.
Hey, Chopper, what do you
think that is over there?
What?
All right, Mr.
Giant Fruit, you're all mine.
Oh, that hurt.
Why is this thing so hard?
Hey, Usopp. Yeah?
Got some fruit for you.
You practically crammed
my brain into my chest!
What's wrong with you?
Wait up, Robin, baby!
I've got a present for you.
An island flower.
And one for...
Nami!
Nami, baby, where'd you run off to?
I've got a gift for you!
I can't believe I want
a chair made of cloud.
I wonder if they have a factory
that makes all this stuff.
This cloud is different
from the stuff on the beach.
It's a lot of fun, too.
I didn't figure on getting
wet walking through clouds.
What's that?
Sorry.
What do we have here?
Some kind of fox.
Is that music?
Look.
There's someone over there.
On that cloud.
Oh, great.
It's another monster.
Where's the whistle?
We can ask the Second to save us.
No, we can't.
That's not who you think it is.
That right there is an angel.
An angel?
Esso?
Sue, come here. Sue?
Did you come from the Blue Sea World?
If that's what you call it, we sealed
up a river of clouds to get here.
Speaking of here, is this your home?
Yes, it sure is.
And I'd like to welcome you
to Skypia's Angel Beach.
I bet you'd like to drink that.
The top of a konash is as hard as steel.
It's impossible to crack, so you have
to cut through the underside, like this.
Here you go.
If it's that good, I gotta try some!
Come on, give it to me!
My name is Conis, and
this little one is Sue.
She's a cloud fox.
If you need anything at all,
please let me be of service.
Yeah, about that.
Your eyes are setting my heart on...
Lay off.
Actually, we've got tons of questions.
I hate to bother you, but we've
never been anyplace like this before.
Sure, ask me anything you
want to know. Guys, look.
Something's coming.
Oh, that's my father.
House, Conis!
House, father!
Can't you say hello like normal people?
Conis, what's that thing he's riding on?
Ah, that would be my father's waver.
Whoa, that's awesome!
A sky waver.
Gangway!
Stopping this thing is a bit of a trick!
My goodness, is everyone all right?
You're the one who crashed!
Hey, Luffy, didn't you bring back
something like that waver from the seabed?
Oh, yeah, I did, didn't I?
Then that must be the boat we read
about in that Noland the Liar book,
a boat that can sail without wind!
Did you make some new
friends? Conis, my dear? Yes.
They arrived only a few minutes
ago from the Blue Sea World.
Oh, still adjusting.
There must be a great many things that
puzzle you about the White White Sea.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
Forgive me for not
introducing myself sooner.
My name is Pagaya.
Oh, it's very nice to meet you.
So, Father, how was the fishing today?
Quite a successful venture.
I have an idea.
You should all come over for dinner.
We'll fill your bellies with
the taste of the island.
Come out for that! I'm starving!
Sky Island Cuisine?
Do you mind if I help you prepare it?
No.
Before we go, I have a question.
This boat, it doesn't have
any sails to catch the wind,
and you weren't rowing it either.
So, how's it propelled through the water?
Oh, of course.
Your people aren't familiar
with dials, are they?
Order dials!
Ah!
Oh, no.
I hope he's all right.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have let a
rookie use the waiver.
Since Luffy can't swim, I hope
this sea is more buoyant than ours.
Maybe.
If it can stay floating in the
air, then you're probably right.
We can handle it.
He sank.
That's not the first time I've been wrong.
Ah!
I'll save you!
That was close. Close?
You were standing on the beach.
What do you know about close?
Oh, yeah, and thanks for
all the help, by the way.
Is it really necessary
for you to jump in, too?
Sky Island's scary!
I apologize for letting
him take the waver out.
With its light body, even a
small wave can shake the rudder.
Unless you know the white, white
sea like the back of your hand,
the waver is almost impossible to ride.
But Ken, I am sorry.
It's only recently that I
became good enough to ride it.
Whoa, is it really that hard?
It usually takes ten years
of training to drive it.
You've got to be joking!
Wow, look at her go!
This is wonderful!
Oh, Nami, you're a
vision riding that waver!
That's incredible.
I can't believe it.
This is her first time.
Yeah, how come she can do it and I can't?
Wow, this really requires skill.
No wonder you had a hard time, Luffy.
Nami, we're invited to dinner, so get
off that thing and stop being so rude!
Talk about rude.
Stupid Waverhog! Go on ahead.
If it's okay with Peak, yeah, I'd
like to stay out here and ride.
That's fine. Just be careful.
Riding this freely on
the open ocean without
worrying about the wind is like a dream.
I wonder if we can use these
on our ocean back home.
Whoa, is that some kind of factory?
Indeed it is.
That is our cloud quarry site.
It's where our clouds are manufactured
and cut to meet all types of needs.
I didn't know you could cut a cloud.
You did take the Milky Road to get
to the White White Sea, correct?
Milky Road?
Is that the name of that messed
up current we took up here?
Yes.
It's a canal constructed by our engineers
and made using the
natural clouds we quarry.
There are actually two types of
natural clouds on our island.
Your ship traveled atop
what we call sea clouds?
And the ones that float on their own?
That we can stand on and build on?
Are called island clouds.
They're not the normal clouds
that we're used to, are they?
No Their condensation
nucleus is different!
From what you usually see?
It has to do with a mineral found in the
blue sea world Called sea prism stone.
Sea prism stone What effect
does that have on the clouds?
It's like this.
Inside the sea prism
are carnelian particles.
Called pyrobrine.
During volcanic eruptions, these particles
gain moisture and descend into the sky.
Our clouds are formed based on
the density of the moisture.
Oh, yeah, I heard about those things.
Sure!
I remember that from when I was a kid.
We used to always play with
carnelian particles in the yard.
Enough sarcasm!
In all actuality, there are three types
of clouds that we use in our day-to-day.
The sea and island types are natural.
The man-made ones come from island clouds.
Now, if you'll follow me, please.
Check out the view from up here. Look!
If you squint, you can
see Nami riding the waver.
Luffy, what are you waiting on?
How come she's so good
at that stupid thing?
Fall off!
Cut it out.
Thanks, Sonja.
You just made me bite my tongue.
I'm bleeding. Poor baby.
Hey, Pagaya, which way to the kitchen?
It's right up here.
What happened to you?
Well, I saw this stuff sitting
in your fridge and I, uh,
I'd never seen anything like it, so I
tried it and, and it tastes like death.
Now I'm all dizzy and
my tongue feels swollen.
How's it look?
Like you drank some spoiled sauce.
Then why did you leave
this stuff sitting around?
Sounds like you're having
fun in the kitchen.
I bet Sanji's just excited about Sky
Island food being such a new thing.
So, uh, I was wondering,
could you explain some more to us about
these dials you mentioned earlier?
Sure.
But it's complex.
I don't exactly know where to start.
Ah, I've never been this relaxed.
Hmm.
This doesn't look like a
dial, it's just a seashell.
Yes, at first glance, but why don't
you put it to your mouth and talk?
Usopp Sting!
Why do you always pick on me?
Now, just press down
the apex of the shell.
Wanna tell me what an apex is?
It means vertex, our highest point.
Usopp Sting!
The seashell's making fun of Usopp too!
What did I ever do to you, seashell?
Now, just press down
the apex of the shell.
Hey, that's a neat trick.
So we can store any
sound and play it back?
Then that shell is one of the dials.
Yes, we call this one a tone dial.
It's a shell from the white, white sea
that records and replays whatever it hears.
Hey, hold on.
I didn't think there was
a bottom to your sea.
Where do these things live, anyway?
They live in the shallows
in the cloud reefs.
I still don't see how that little thing
could move your father's sky waver.
Well, that's because this is
the kind that powers the waver.
It's smaller, but it does
demonstrate the same process.
Here, let me show you.
So this one blows wind
out of its backside.
Let me see.
This is called a breath dial.
It allows you the ability to store
the wind and expel it at your desire.
The wind capacity varies depending
on the size of the shell.
If you attach the right size to the stern
of a ship You can move along swiftly.
I've never heard of anything like that.
I get it now.
The waver moved by blowing a stream of
wind through the water that waver is fun.
Dials don't just power wavers.
There's also the skating
kind of the board kind But I
don't go for those the wavers
about as crazy as I get.
I wish I was out there on
that thing instead of Nami.
And I could be if I could figure
out how to fix the one we have.
How did you ever find
a waver in your world?
Well, it's kind of hard to
even tell if that's what it is.
You know that hunk of
junk is 200 years old
in a total wreck There's no way it works.
That might not be the case.
Dials are made from the
remains of dead shellfish.
They can last indefinitely so long
as the shell itself isn't broken.
You might get lucky.
I told you so!
You never said anything like that.
I know.
I'd venture a guess there
are many types of dials.
Is this one here?
Yes, that's a lamp dial.
Heat!
It lit up from inside!
Right!
There are flame dials
that store heat and fire,
Flavor dials that store
various tastes and aromas.
And vision dials that store
everything the user sees.
Which you can watch again and again?
I want to live in the clouds
for the rest of my life!
To be honest,
we couldn't really sustain life here
in the clouds without these dials.
Our culture has evolved with the dials.
I suppose in the same way they
evolved with the white white sea.
Ladies and gentlemen, dinner is served.
We have for you Sky
Lobster with special sauce
and a side of island fruits
that I can't pronounce.
That looks so good!
Let's dig in!
Oh, wow, it tastes sweet!
I wouldn't have expected it from lobster.
Yum!
Hey, guys, any of you know where Nami is?
I think she's riding the Waver.
I don't see her.
She probably went out too far.
She's like that.
Who cares?
You should have some of this.
I'm worried.
Do you think she's okay?
I have my concerns, but I
can't say one way or the other.
What are you talking about?
In the clouds,
there's a place called the Upper Yard that
no one is ever allowed to set foot on.
It's not too far away.
It would only be a short
trip by Waver from here.
I'm afraid your friend Nami might have
set ashore there out of curiosity.
They're huge!
What is this?
What's so bad that no one can
ever go over to this island?
Is it full of monsters?
It's sacred ground. Sacred ground?
But it's so much more than just that.
It's the island where God lives.
Thank you.